<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RSP</string>

    <string name="btnOK">OK</string>
    <string name="btnCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="btnChooseContact">choose\na contact</string>
    <string name="btnSwitch">start a programm</string>

    <string name="titleActivityMaps">Map</string>
    <string name="titleActivityBook">Contacts</string>

    <string name="actionBtnInstructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="actionBtnDevelopers">Developers</string>
    <string name="actionBtnFromDeveloper">More from developer</string>
    <string name="actionBtnAdviseFriend">Advise a friend</string>
    <string name="actionBtnFeedback">Feedback</string>

    <array name="arrWorkers">
        <item>Developer Matatov Yury</item>
        <item>Designer Matatov Nikita</item>
    </array>

    <string name="toastSendMail">Message sent.</string>

    <string name="textSMSnewSimWithLocal">On the device of your friend changed the sim card. Contact him and find out what\'s wrong. Coordinates: https://www.google.com/maps/search/?api=1&amp;query=%1$s,%2$s. RSP</string>
    <string name="textSMSnewSimWithoutLocal">On the device of your friend changed the sim card. Contact him and find out what\'s wrong. Phone coordinates absent. RSP</string>
    <string name="textSMSFirst">I chose you for the Remote Security Phone program as a recipient of notifications for replacing a sim card with my phone. Thanks.</string>

    <string name="dialogPermissionSMS">Permission to send sms messages is necessary to automatically alert the selected contact about the replacement of the sim card. For sending sms messages may be charged. You can get the details from your mobile operator.</string>
    <string name="dialogPermissionContact">Contact permission is necessary to select a contact as the recipient of the notification about the replacement of a sim card. Do not worry, the phone book data is available only to the user of the program.</string>
    <string name="dialogPermissionPhoneState">Permission to manage phone calls is necessary to determine the replacement of a sim card. Do not worry, all telephone data is available only to the user of the program.</string>
    <string name="dialogPermissionLocation">Permission to the location of the device is necessary to determine the coordinates of the device when replacing the sim card and will sending notification in the form of sms on the selected contact.</string>

    <string name="textNeedChooseContact">For the program to work correctly, you must select a contact who will receive a notification if the card is replaced. It is desirable that this was a person whom you trust!</string>
    <string name="textInstructions">Welcome to the Remote Protection service of your phone. To start the application, you need to select a contact that will receive SMS messages in the event that your device is lost and the SIM card is replaced. Note! The program will not work if the attacker formats the phone before replacing the SIM card or simply deletes the program.</string>
    <string name="textPrivacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="titleMarkerMap">Your device</string>
    <string name="textChooseContact">Contact receiving notification:\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="textNotChooseContact">not selected</string>
    <string name="textNotification">Click to see location device.</string>
    <string name="textVersion">Version 4.3</string>

</resources>